## Yaskarina Alt. Nunez

211 Madison Ave, Perth Amboy, NJ Yaskarina123@gmail.com

(732) 423-0409 Nunezjiy@Kean.Edu

## Summary

Progressively working on the second college degree. Computer technical and active skills with fourteen years of experience in the field in different positions. Worked on the development of skills to keep up with the new technology and systems. Strong written and oral communication skills in Spanish and developing communication skills in English.

### **Education**

Kean University, Union, NJ Major in Computer Science

Expected Graduation Due: September 2023

• **GPA** 3.44

Middlesex Community College, Perth Amboy, NJ Transfer September 2017

UCATECI, La Vega, RD Major in Computer Engineering Graduated on March 2002

#### **Skills and Abilities**

#### **Technical Skills**

- Studied Oracle development and database PL/SQL
- Putty
- Java
- Microsoft Office (Windows, Excel, PowerPoint)

## Non-Technical Skills

- Client relations
- Conflict Resolution Techniques
- Research ability
- Talent development
- Customer service
- Skilled multi-tasker
- Schedule coordination oriented

# Languages

- Fluent in Spanish
- Efficient in English

# Employment Experience

Oct 2003 - April 2004

Cooperativa Vega Real, La Vega. RD

• Customer Service

Attend all coming customers with what they need from the corporative and/or transactions.

May 2004 – December 2005

Cooperativa Vega Real, La Vega. RD

• IT Support

Provide aid with the systems and any computer issues in the different offices of the corporative.

January 2006 – June 2015

Cooperativa Vega Real, La Vega. RD

Manager of the Computer Department

Provider of technological aid and consultation for business. Making upgrades to the existing system.

Nov 2019 – August 2021

Vega Real Corporation, Perth Amboy, NJ

• Administrative Assistant

Provider of friendly and knowledgeable service for routine questions and service of the benefits provided by the company.

# **Honors**

Honorable mention in Kean University for school achievements:

- January 2022
- Spring 2021 on July 2021